GABRIELA DOMÍNGUEZ

PHP Developer

gaby.dommm@gmail.com	My Portfolio	+52 646-193-41-38	<u>LinkedIn</u>

SUMMARY: Developer with 3 years of experience who enjoys working in an agile environment and has a passion for problem-solving. Used to work in a fast-paced environment whilst multi-tasking and consistently meeting deadlines.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PHP Developer (Product Information Management) | Softtek Jul 2019 - Present | Ensenada, B.C. Mexico

- Pimcore environment setup using its official Docker image.
- Symfony events and event listeners.
- Management of assets, roles, layouts, and workflows.
- Cronjobs for management of marketing features.
- Usage of .NET using C# for specific features
- Cache implementation in endpoints (time reduction of 44.4%).
- Unit and Integration testing (PHP Unit).
- Development of API endpoints (REST, JSON, etc.).
- UX/UI for product Previews/Iframe Panels.
- Teamwork in order to find technical solutions. Pair programming. Code reviews. Documentation in Confluence.
- Worked collaboratively with other developers, designers, business analysts/Product Owners, QA team, etc.
- Worked with remote team members.
- Customer service and support. End user training.
- Led meetings with International customers.

Java Academy Trainee | Softtek

Jan 2019 - May 2019 | Ensenada, B.C. Mexico

- Took courses as part of the Java Academy Program, including Advanced Java, Maven, Spring 4, Web Services, CSS, Angular 5, Git, MVC, and Best Practices on a general level.

Business Analyst Internship | LKMX Aug 2018 – Jan 2019 | Ensenada, B.C. Mexico

- Definition of User Stories. Backlog grooming.
- Participation in Scrum ceremonies.
- Constant communication with the stakeholders

TECHNI	ΙΔΟΙ	SKII	15
ILCHIN		JIVIL	_LJ

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux

Programming languages: PHP (2 years), Java (5 months), Python (3 years, for school purposes), Javascript (1/2 year)

Frameworks: Symfony 4, Spring 4

Databases: MariaDB (2 years), MySQL (1 year), SQL Server (4 months)

Methodologies: SCRUM (3+ years) alongside with JIRA and Confluence

Other: Pimcore 6, PHP Unit, Apache, Docker, Git, Bitbucket, GitLab, HTML, CSS, Twig, JQuery,

GraphQL, Jenkins, UML, Postman, Visual Studio Code (VSC), MVC, Object-Oriented

Programming (OOP), LAMP environment

EDUCATION

Universidad Autónoma de Baja California

B. S. Computer Science 2014 – 2018 Baja California, Mexico

University of Regina

International Student Exchange Program (Computer Science) 2018-1 Saskatchewan, Canada

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

Organized, responsible, multitasking, persevering, ease of speech, disciplined, initiative for problem solving

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native), English (Advanced), French (Intermediate)